<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<kiln:root xmlns:i18n="http://apache.org/cocoon/i18n/2.1"
           xmlns:kiln="http://www.kcl.ac.uk/artshums/depts/ddh/kiln/ns/1.0"
           xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
           xmlns:xsl="http://www.w3.org/1999/XSL/Transform">

  <kiln:parent>
    <xi:include href="base.xml" />
  </kiln:parent>

  <kiln:child>
    <kiln:block name="title">
      <i18n:text>home-title</i18n:text>
    </kiln:block>

    <kiln:block name="page-header">
      <div class="row">
        <div class="large-12 columns text-center">
          <h1>
            <!--<span class="round label">-->
              <i18n:text i18n:key="home-title">Inscriptions of Roman Cyrenaica</i18n:text>
            <!--</span>-->
          </h1>
        </div>
      </div>
    </kiln:block>

    <kiln:block name="content-section">
      <main>
        <!--<div class="row">
          <div class="small-6 large-centered columns">
            <p>Now that you have EFES up and running, it's time to
            start building your project. Start with one of the options
            listed below and go from there.</p>
          </div>
        </div>-->
        <div class="row">
          <div class="large-12 columns">
            <div class="panel radius">
              <p>In 1948 Joyce Reynolds, of Newnham College Cambridge, then based at the British
                School at Rome, started a series of regular visits to Libya, to study the
                inscriptions of the Roman period. She worked initially in Tripolitania: her
                epigraphic corpus, the <i>Inscriptions of Roman Tripolitania</i>, written with John
                Ward-Perkins, was published in 1952, and an aenhanced edition was published online in 2009:
                <a href="http://inslib.kcl.ac.uk/irt2009/">Inscriptions of Roman Tripolitania (2009)</a>. In 1951 she
                first visited Cyrenaica, and since then has collected and studied the inscriptions of Roman
                Cyrenaica, working with local archaeologists and others from Italy, France, the U.K.
                and the U.S.A.. She continued to visit Libya almost every year until 2008, and
                 assembled materials for a corpus of over 2000 inscriptions from Roman Cyrenaica.
                Nearly a third of these have never previously been published, while others have only
                appeared in versions which can be very much improved, and better understood, as a
                result of re-reading. The majority are accompanied by photographs collected by Joyce Reynolds and her colleagues 
                (in particular Elizabeth Rosenbaum-Alföldi and Hafed Walda), 
                or given to her by the Libyan Department of Antiquities.</p>
            </div>
          </div>
          <div class="large-12 columns">
            <div class="panel radius">
              <p>The
                Inscriptions of Roman Cyrenaica project was initially funded by the Leverhulme Trust, to
                publish this material as an online corpus, and has received further funding from the Society for Libyan Studies. 
                The team draws on experience gained in publishing the online corpora of the
                <a href="http://insaph.kcl.ac.uk/" class="ext" title="External website">Inscriptions
                  of Aphrodisias</a>, and <a href="http://iospe.kcl.ac.uk">Ancient Inscriptions of the Northern Black Sea</a>. The new corpus is presented as a
                series of documents; but as part of the project we have created and published the 
                <a href="https://www.slsgazetteer.org/">Heritage Gazetteer of Libya</a>, to which the corpus refers. We 
                have worked in close co-operation with the <a href="https://igcyr.unibo.it/">Inscriptions of Roman Cyrenaica/Greek Verse Inscriptions of Cyrenaica</a> 
                project, to our mutual benefit.</p>
            </div>
          </div>
          <!--<div class="large-4 columns">
            <div class="panel radius">
              <p><strong>Read the documentation</strong></p>

              <p>The documentation and User Guide for  
                       EFES can be found on the project's <a href="https://github.com/EpiDoc/EFES/wiki/">GitHub Wiki pages</a>. 
                       Documentation for Kiln, the platform that EFES is based on, can be found both <a
                     href="http://kiln.readthedocs.org/en/latest/">online</a>, and in source form, in the docs directory of your
              installation. It explains how you can modify everything
              about your project.</p>
            </div>
          </div>-->
        </div>
      </main>
    </kiln:block>
  </kiln:child>
</kiln:root>
